{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi6.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "amazing"
            ],
            "answer": "amazing, fascinating",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1489773712.8671615,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"affascinante\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le forbici",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1489773669.40733,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scissors\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pericoloso",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1489773717.4270496,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dangerous\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "affascinante",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1489773746.8789246,
            "question": "Given the definition \"amazing, fascinating\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "curly",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773686.5355191,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"riccio\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'attesa",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773707.6031885,
            "question": "Given the definition \"waiting time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to notice, to note"
            ],
            "answer": "to notice, note",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773649.2514832,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"notare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to worry",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773704.487374,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"preoccuparsi\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fissare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773759.5025578,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to set\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "liscio",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773774.1069171,
            "question": "Given the definition \"straight\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be located",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773445.8244534,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"trovarsi\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straight",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773551.1636384,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"liscio\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "esitare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773038.4070559,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hesitate\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stairs",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773136.2775314,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le scale\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "attraversare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773769.6426666,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to cross\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "trovarsi",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773592.4038243,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be located\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "farsi tagliare i capelli",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773264.3058062,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get a hair cut\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "per fortuna",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489772932.8797288,
            "question": "Given the definition \"luckily, fortunately\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scissors",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773438.0086854,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le forbici\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "accompagnare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773134.206275,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to accompany\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "troppo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773019.011232,
            "question": "Given the definition \"too, too much\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "capace",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773035.9435349,
            "question": "Given the definition \"able, capable\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "smile",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489772779.2942393,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il sorriso\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "notare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1489773607.3434663,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to notice, note\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "all around",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773529.5759997,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tutt'intorno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to set",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773534.9675727,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fissare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capable"
            ],
            "answer": "able, capable",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773033.943418,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"capace\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tutt'intorno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773533.0483096,
            "question": "Given the definition \"all around\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il bariere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773540.9401636,
            "question": "Given the definition \"barber\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "too, too much",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489773603.9676309,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"troppo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nessuno",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773509.052467,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nobody, no one\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to happen",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773203.9536722,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"succedere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "riccio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773359.564932,
            "question": "Given the definition \"curly\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il turno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773579.6918306,
            "question": "Given the definition \"turn; shift\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "every time, each time"
            ],
            "answer": "each time, every time",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773102.0545716,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ogni volta\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scendere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772744.1750162,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to descend\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to cross",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773206.7457223,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"attraversare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nobody, no one",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773119.250214,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nessuno\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ricordare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773377.569247,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to remember, to remind\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il negozio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773243.4786253,
            "question": "Given the definition \"store\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "senza",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489773595.3318415,
            "question": "Given the definition \"without\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "road",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772923.592772,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la strada\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il sorriso",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773366.448747,
            "question": "Given the definition \"smile\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get a hair cut",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772921.4802318,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"farsi tagliare i capelli\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to remember, to remind",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773005.571606,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ricordare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "succedere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772776.5700533,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to happen\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to come",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773016.6352818,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"venire\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lontano da",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772761.3667781,
            "question": "Given the definition \"far from\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ogni volta",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773115.9299247,
            "question": "Given the definition \"each time, every time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la strada",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773094.6620424,
            "question": "Given the definition \"road\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "barber",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489772915.5047085,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il bariere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dangerous",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773561.8801842,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pericoloso\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "turn",
                "turn, shift"
            ],
            "answer": "turn; shift",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489773558.2839446,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il turno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fortunately"
            ],
            "answer": "luckily, fortunately",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489772940.6318197,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"per fortuna\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "without",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489772950.572241,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"senza\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "store",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489772873.64942,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il negozio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "waiting time",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773486.1401124,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'attesa\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "venire",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773074.562664,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to come\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to descend",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489772895.988866,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scendere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le scale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773142.7576358,
            "question": "Given the definition \"stairs\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "preoccuparsi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489772861.4410572,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to worry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "far from",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773183.1219516,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lontano da\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hesitate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773068.6906967,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"esitare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to accompany",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489773299.57368,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"accompagnare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}